Indiana University President's Office records, 1962-1968 C304
Indiana University Archives
- Subject files, 1962-1968
  - City Securities Corporation, 1962 (Box 34)
  - Civil Defense (Box 34)
    - License - Fallout Shelter (Fort Wayne), 1962 (Box 34)
    - General (Box 34)
      - 1962-1963 (Box 34)
      - 1963-1964 (Box 34)
  - Civil Defense Program (Box 34)
    - 1964-1965 (Box 34)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 34)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 34)
  - License-Civil Defense, Fallout Shelter (Fort Wayne), 1962 (Box 34)
  - Civil Rights, 1965-1968; (2 folders) (Box 34)
  - Cl, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 34)
  - Clar, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 34)
  - Clark, David L., 1965-1968; (3 folders) (Box 34)
  - Clark, Thomas D., 1966 (Box 34)
  - Class Period-Proposed Change from 45 to 60 minutes, 1965-1966 (Box 34)
  - Cle general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 34)
  - Co, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 34)
  - Coh, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 34)
  - Col, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 34)
  - Cold Storage Plant, Annual Report, 1967-1968 (Box 34)
  - Coll general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 34)
  - College of Arts and Sciences (Box 34)
    - 1964-1965 (Box 34)
    - Faculty Minutes and Committee, 1964-1965 (Box 34)
  - College Entrance Examination Board, 1965-1968 (Box 34)
  - College and University Reports, 1965-1968 (Box 35)
  - College Life Insurance Company of America, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 35)
    - Convention French Lick, Sheraton, August 23, 1966 (Box 35)
  - College Management, 1965-1966 (Box 35)
  - Collins, Ralph (Box 35)
    - 1962-1963, (2 folders) (Box 35)
    - Auditorium-Ballantine Hall, 1963-1967 (Box 35)
    - Memorial Lectureship, 1963-1965 (Box 35)
  - Columbia Club, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 35)
  - Columbia University, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 35)
  - Com, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 35)
  - Commencement (Box 35)
    - 1966-1968, (2 folders) (Box 35)
    - Air Force and Army ROTC, 1968 (Box 35)
    - IPFW, 1968 (Box 35)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 35)
    - Bloomington Campus, the New Stadium, June 12, 1967 (Box 35)
    - 1962-1966, (5 folders) (Box 35)
  - Commission on the Humanities (National Foundation on the Arts and Humanities), 1964-1966; (3 folders) (Box 35)
  - Committees (Box 35)
    - A-E, 1966-1968 (Box 35)
    - F-Q, 1962-1968 (Box 35)
    - R-Z, 1963-1968 (Box 35)
    - 1964-1966, (2 folders) (Box 35)
  - Committees (Box 36)
    - 1962-1964, (2 folders) (Box 36)
    - Committee Acceptances and Declinations, 1962-1967; (5 folders) (Box 36)
    - Committee Letters (Box 36)
      - by Committee, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 36)
      - by Member, 1963-1968; (4 folders) (Box 36)
    - Student participation on University committees, 1965-1966 (Box 36)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Memos, 1966-1968 (Box 36)
    - Committee Appointments for 1968-1969 (Box 36)
    - Work Folder, 1964-1965 (Box 36)
    - Committee List (Box 36)
      - 1962-1968, (4 folders) (Box 36)
      - By members, 1964-1968 (Box 36)
      - External Committee List, 1962-1965; (2 folders) (Box 36)
      - Distribution, 1963-1964 (Box 36)
      - Student membership, 1967-1968 (Box 36)
    - Committee for academic development, 1961-1968; (2 folders) (Box 36)
    - Committee on Academic Freedom, undated (Box 36)
    - Administrative committee minutes, 1962-1965; (5 folders) (Box 36)
    - Administrative committee minutes, 1964-1968; (7 folders) (Box 37)
    - Admissions committee, 1965-1968; (3 folders) (Box 37)
    - Committee on Admissions, Feb.-May 1963 (Box 37)
    - Advisory policy committee for data systems and services, 1966-1968; (2 folders) (Box 37)
    - Advisory committee on computer development, 1967-1968 (Box 37)
    - Advisory committee to the President of Indiana University, 1962-1963 (Box 37)
    - Advisory committee, 1963-1968; (2 folders) (Box 37)
    - Advisory committee on International Studies, 1964-1965 (Box 37)
    - Advisory committee appointed by the President, 1965 (Box 37)
    - Aerospace Research Application Center, committees and advisory board, 1963-1968; (4 folders) (Box 37)
    - Committee on aged and aging, 1962-1967; (4 folders) (Box 37)
    - Animal Farm Planning Committee, 1966-1968 (Box 37)
    - Committee on the arts, 1966-1967 (Box 37)
    - Committee for Deanship of the College of Arts and Sciences, 1963-1966; (2 folders) (Box 37)
    - Asian Studies Review Committee, ad hoc, 1965 (Box 37)
    - Atterbury Job Corps Center Policy Committee, ad hoc, 1965 (Box 37)
    - Biomedical Sciences Support Grant Committee, Jan.-May 1968 (Box 37)
    - Committee on building names, 1963-1968; (5 folders) (Box 37)
    - Bradford Woods advisory committee, 1966-1968 (Box 37)
    - Business and Financial Policy, 1959-1965 (Box 37)
    - Business and Finance Policy, 1963-1965; (3 folders) (Box 37)
    - Campus Planning Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 37)
    - Committee for Chancellor of Indiana University at Indianapolis, 1968 (Box 37)
    - Chemical Physics Committee, 1961-1962 (Box 37)
    - Commencement Committee, 1963-1967 (Box 38)
    - Comparative Literature Committee, 1962-1964 (Box 38)
    - Committee on computer assisted instruction, 1966-1968 (Box 38)
    - Committee on computer development, 1967-1968 (Box 38)
    - Computer Center Coordinating Committee, Sep.-Oct. 1964 (Box 38)
    - Computer Science Committee, Mar.-Oct. 1965 (Box 38)
    - Continuing Committee of Concerned Faculty, Feb. 1968 (Box 38)
    - Coordinating Committee for the Center for Instructional Resources and Services, 1964-1965 (Box 38)
    - Curricular Policies and Educational Program Committee, 1962-1968 (Box 38)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1964-1968 (Box 38)
    - Committee for the Deanship for the School of Education, 1965-1966 (Box 38)
    - Committee for the Deanship of the Indianapolis Regional Campus, 1965-1966 (Box 38)
    - Committee on Dedication of Buildings, 1962-1968; (4 folders) (Box 38)
    - Dedications Committee (Box 38)
      - Auditorium Organ, 1967-1968 (Box 38)
      - Preventive Dentistry Building, 1967-1968 (Box 38)
      - Geology Building, Mar. 1963-May 1964 (Box 38)
      - McNutt Quadrangle, 1967-1968; (2 folders) (Box 38)
      - Museum, Oct. 1965 (Box 38)
      - Optometry, 1967-1968 (Box 38)
      - Psychology, 1963 (Box 38)
      - Rawles Hall, 1967-1968 (Box 38)
      - Riley Hospital, 1964-1967 (Box 38)
      - Student Health Center, 1965 (Box 38)
      - Track, 1966 (Box 38)
      - IU-Purdue Foundation, 1963-1964 (Box 38)
      - University School, 1964 (Box 38)
    - Committee on the Fort Wayne Dedication, 1964-1966 (Box 38)
    - Committee on dedication of Kokomo Campus, 1963-1966 (Box 38)
    - Committee to Study the Ph.D. and the Ed.D., Oct.-Nov. 1964 (Box 38)
    - Committee on distinguished faculty ranks, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 38)
    - Drafts—Committees, 1967-1968 (Box 38)
    - Domicile Committee, 1963-1968 (Box 38)
    - Committee for Economic Development, 1967-1968; (5 folders) (Box 38)
    - Committee for Economic Development, 1964-1967; (13 folders) (Box 39)
    - Committee for Economic Development (Box 40)
      - 1963-1964, (2 folders) (Box 40)
      - Research and Policy Committee, 1962 (Box 40)
      - Advisory Board, 1967-1968 (Box 40)
      - (Indiana Magazine of History) Editorial Committee, 1962-1968 (Box 40)
      - Committee on (John H.) Edward's Award, 1968 (Box 40)
      - Environmental Health Committee, 1965-1968; (3 folders) (Box 40)
    - Committee for Equality of Higher Educational Opportunity, 1964-1968 (Box 40)
      - (Folder 1) (Box 40)
      - (Folder 2) (Box 40)
    - Report of the Committee on Equality of Higher Educational Opportunity, 19 January 1965 (Box 40)
    - Indiana University Committee on Equality of Educational Opportunity (Box 40)
      - 1965-1966 (Box 40)
      - 1966-1968 (Box 40)
    - Committee on Equality of Educational Opportunity (Box 40)
      - 1964-1965 (Box 40)
      - Texas Southern University, 1964-1965 (Box 40)
    - Committee on Expanding Educational Opportunity, 1966-1967 (Box 40)
    - Committee-Equipment Committee, 1962-1966; (2 folders) (Box 40)
    - Committee on Exchange of Persons (Conference Board of Associated Research Councils), 1962-1963 (Box 40)
    - Faculty Committee, 1962-1968; (2 folders) (Box 40)
    - Committee-Faculty Communications—Agenda Items, Minutes, and General Correspondence, 1965-1968 (Box 40)
    - Faculty Communications, Committee on, 1967-1968 (Box 40)
    - Committee to plan the dinner for the retiring faculty, 1963-1968 (Box 40)
    - Foreign Student Advisory Committee, 1963-1968; (2 folders) (Box 40)
    - Committee on Foreign Students, 1963-1964 (Box 40)
    - Committee to consider the feasibility and desirability of an expanded program in the forensic sciences, ad hoc, Feb.-Sep. 1965 (Box 40)
    - Committees-Founder's Day Committee, 1962-1968; (2 folders) (Box 40)
    - Fraternity and Sorority Affairs Committee, Apr.-May 1968 (Box 40)
    - Committee-Fringe Benefit Committee, 1962-1967; (2 folders) (Box 40)
    - Committee for Further Study on an Indiana University Scholarly Journal, Jul. 1964 (Box 40)
    - Committee for Further Study on an Indiana University Scholarly Journal, 1962-1964 (Box 41)
    - Committee for Government of the People, Reapportionment Issues (Dirksen Amendment SJR 103), Jan. 1966 (Box 41)
    - Committee-Graduate Advisory, Indianapolis, 1966-1968; (2 folders) (Box 41)
    - Committee-Graduate School T.A., Nov.-Dec. 1968 (Box 41)
    - Fee Remission Scholarships-Graduate Student Support Subcommittee, 10 Oct. 1967 (Box 41)
    - Searching and Screening Committee for Position of Vice President for Graduate Development, Ad Hoc, 1964-1965 (Box 41)
    - Committees on the Review of Graduate Education at Indiana University-Indianapolis, 1967-1968 (Box 41)
    - University Grievance Committee on Discriminatory Practices, 29 Feb. 1968 (Box 41)
    - Committee—Halls of Residence (Box 41)
      - 1962-1968, (5 folders) (Box 41)
      - Housing Planning Committee (conference), 1962-1963 (Box 41)
    - Committee—Health, Physical Education, and Recreation, School of, Search and Screening Committee to interview and recommend candidates for the Deanship, 1966-1967 (Box 41)
    - Committee to help plan the university's participation in Indiana's sesquicentennial, 1964-1965 (Box 41)
    - Committee—Higher Education Personnel Training, May-Jun. 1968 (Box 41)
    - Committee—Honorary Degrees, 1962-1968 (Box 41)
    - Committee—Honors (University), 1962-1966 (Box 41)
    - Committee—Honors, 1962 (Box 41)
    - Committee—Honors Division, Searching and Screening for a Director, Feb.-Oct. 1966 (Box 41)
    - Committee—Human Resources Development, 1966-1968 (Box 41)
    - Committee on the Humanities, Arts, Social Science, Law, and Education, 1964 (Box 41)
    - Committee on improvement of teaching, 1964 (Box 41)
    - Committee—Inaugural Committee, 1962 (Box 41)
    - Committee—Indiana Language Program Advisory, 1962-1965; (5 folders) (Box 41)
    - Committee—Indianapolis Metropolitan Area Committee to study Higher Education, 1962-1963 (Box 41)
    - Committee—Information Processing (University Advisory Committee on), 1968; (2 folders) (Box 41)
    - Committee on Institutional Cooperation, 1962-1968; (2 folders) (Box 41)
    - Committee on Instructional Television, 1965-1966; (2 folders) (Box 41)
    - Committee on Insurance and Retirement, 1962-1968; (3 folders) (Box 41)
    - Committee—International Affairs (Box 41)
      - 1964-1968, (3 folders) (Box 41)
      - Byrnes Committee, 1966 (Box 41)
      - Survey of World Affairs Activities of Indiana University, 1964 (Box 41)
      - United States Higher Education and World Affairs (Bibliography prepared by Richard F. Crabbs and Frank W. Holmquist), Sep. 1965 (Box 42)
      - University Committee, 1963-1968; (7 folders) (Box 42)
    - Committee on International Exchange of Persons, 1964; (2 folders) (Box 42)
    - Committee—International Grants, 1965-1968; (92 folders) (Box 42)
    - Committee—International Grants, 1965 (Box 42)
    - Committee on International Relations, 1963-1964 (Box 42)
    - International Relations Committee and Advisory Committee on International Studies, 1963 (Box 42)
    - Committee on International Studies, 1964-1965; (2 folders) (Box 42)
    - Committee—Junior Division, 1962-1963 (Box 42)
    - Committee—Labor Advisory, 1964-1965; 1968; (2 folders) (Box 42)
    - Faculty Committee on Faculties for Large Group Instruction, 1965-1968; (3 folders) (Box 43)
    - Committee—Searching and Screening for the Deanship of the School of Law, 1965-1966 (Box 43)
    - Committee—Search and screening for dean of Law, Indianapolis, 1966-1967 (Box 43)
    - Committee—Legislative Advisory, report to Admin. Comm.. on visit, 12/4/1963 (Box 43)
    - Committee—Legislative Assistantship Advisory 1963, undated; (5 folders) (Box 43)
    - Committee—Faculty Library, 1963-1968; (4 folders) (Box 43)
    - Committee—Lilly Library Advisory, 1962-1963 (Box 43)
    - Committee—Library Review and Planning, 1962-1963; 1968; (5 folders) (Box 43)
    - Committee—for a director of the division of Library Science, Search and Screening, 1965-1966; (2 folders) (Box 43)
    - Committee List, 1966-1968; (2 folders) (Box 43)
      - Work papers for master list, 1966-1967 (Box 43)
      - 1965-1966 (Box 43)
      - External committees, 1966 (Box 43)
    - Committee—Medical Center Academic Advisory, 1964-1965; undated; (3 folders) (Box 43)
    - Committee on Training and research in Mental retardation, interdisciplinary, 1966 (Box 43)
    - Committee for Model Cities Program, all university, 1967-1968 (Box 43)
    - Committee to Coordinate and promote national aeronautics and space administration projects at Indiana University, 1962 (Box 43)
    - Committee to develop policies for control and management of the outdoor swimming pool, 1965 (Box 43)
    - Committees outside I.U., 1963-1967 (Box 43)
      - Committee on equal education and employment opportunities, 1961-1966; (3 folders) (Box 43)
      - Miscellaneous, 1962-1963 (Box 43)
    - Committee on the selection of the auditorium organ, 1966-1968 (Box 43)
    - Committee—Parking study, 1966-1968; (3 folders) (Box 43)
    - Committee—Parking study, 1965-1966 (Box 44)
    - Committee—Parking and Traffic, 1963-1966 (Box 44)
    - Committee—Parking, 1965 (Box 44)
    - Committee—Parking and Traffic, 1962-1964; (2 folders) (Box 44)
    - Committee—University Personnel Structure (Salary Administration), 1962 (Box 44)
    - Committee—Policy, 1963 (Box 44)
    - Committee—Position Evaluation, 1963-1968; (2 folders) (Box 44)
    - Committee—Professional Advisory, Development Training Center, 1965-1967 (Box 44)
    - Committee—Professional Advisory, Riley Child Development Center, 1965-1967 (Box 44)
    - Committee—Publications, 1962-1968; (4 folders) (Box 44)
    - Committee—Real Estate Advisory, 1965-1966 (Box 44)
    - Committee—Regional Campus Advisory, 1964-1967; (3 folders) (Box 44)
    - Committee—Regional Campus Coordinating (Lake County), 1966-1967 (Box 44)
    - Committee—Regional Campus Coordinating (Box 44)
      - 1967 (Box 44)
      - Reports, 1967 (Box 44)
      - 1966 (Box 44)
      - Expenses, June 1966-June 1967 (Box 44)
      - Proposals for New Programs: Documents, 1966 (Box 44)
    - Committee—Regional Campus Planning, 1965 (Box 44)
    - Committee—Regional Campuses, Search and Screening, 1966 (Box 44)
    - Committee—Research Computing Center, Policy, 1964-1968; (2 folders) (Box 44)
    - Committee—Research on Learning and Teaching, 1968 (Box 44)
    - Committee—Research Problems in Public Safety, 1962-1965 (Box 44)
    - Committee—Sabbatical Leaves of Absence, 1962-1968 (Box 44)
    - Committee—Schedule, 1962-1967; (3 folders) (Box 44)
    - Committee—Scholarly Journal, 1962 (Box 44)
    - Committee—for Scholarship and Financial Aids, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 44)
    - Committee—School of Medicine Deanship, 1964-March 1965 (Box 44)
    - Committee—University Self-Study (Box 44)
      - 1965-1966 (Box 44)
      - Advisory, 1965 (Box 44)
    - Committee—Steering, 1966-1967 (Box 44)
    - Committee—Sesquicentennial (Box 44)
      - 1964-1968 (Box 44)
      - Advisory to write the History of I.U., June 1967 (Box 44)
    - Committee—Social Service, Search and Screening for a director of the division, 1965-1966 (Box 44)
    - Committee—Space Assignment (Box 45)
      - A-E, 1965-1969 (Box 45)
      - F-Z, 1965-1967 (Box 45)
    - Committee—Space, 1962-1968; (9 folders) (Box 45)
    - Committee—Statewide Education Programs, 1962-1964 (Box 45)
    - Committee—Student Affairs, 1967-1968 (Box 45)
    - Committee—Student Conduct, 1967 (Box 45)
    - Committee—Student Health Center Evaluation, 1967-1968 (Box 45)
    - Committee—On Student Health Insurance, 1966-1968 (Box 45)
    - Committee—Student Honesty, 1965-1968 (Box 45)
    - Committee—on the Undergraduate program in World Affairs, 1962 (Box 45)
    - Committee—University Press, 1962-1963 (Box 45)
    - Committee—University Press Faculty, 1964-1967; (4 folders) (Box 45)
    - Committee—University Schools Operating, 1966 (Box 45)
    - Committee—on University Statutes and Policy (Committee on Codification), 1966 (Box 45)
  - Communism (Box 45)
    - 1965-1967, (2 folders) (Box 45)
    - 1962-1965, (3 folders) (Box 46)
  - CAPS Housing Resolution, 1966 (Box 46)
  - Community Planning, Division of, 1965-1966; (2 folders) (Box 46)
  - Comparative Religion, 1963-1965 (Box 46)
  - Computers, 1967 (Box 46)
  - Con, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 46)
  - Conant, James B., Publications, 1963-1965; (3 folders) (Box 46)
  - Concessions, Indiana University (Box 46)
    - 1963-1968, (5 folders) (Box 46)
    - Annual Report, 1967-1968 (Box 46)
    - Balance sheets, operating statements, 1962-1967; (5 folders) (Box 46)
  - Conferences—outside I.U. (Box 46)
    - 1965-1968, (2 folders) (Box 46)
    - American Merchant Marie Conference, 1966 (Box 46)
    - 1963-1965, (2 folders) (Box 46)
  - Conferences (Box 46)
    - 1964-1968, (2 folders) (Box 46)
    - Conference Board of Associated Research Councils, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 46)
    - Conference Bureau annual report, 1963-1968; (3 folders) (Box 46)
    - Conference on Alcohol and Traffic Safety, 1964 (Box 46)
    - Conference on Higher Education in the United State at Indiana University, February 1965 (Box 46)
    - Conference on International Rural Development, July 27-28, 1964 (Box 46)
    - Conference on Paralanguage and Kinesics, 1962 (Box 46)
    - Conference on Student Stress in the College Experience, November 11-14, 1965 (Box 46)
    - Conference on Theatre Architecture, Campus, 1965 (Box 46)
  - Conservation Foundation, 1965-1966 (Box 46)
  - Construction Planning Report, 1962 (Box 46)
  - Construction Budgeting Office (Box 46)
  - Contemporary Club of Indianapolis, Indianapolis Athletic Club, December 2, 1965 (Box 46)
  - Controller, annual report, 1963-1964 (Box 46)
  - Controversial (Box 46)
    - Church – State relationships, 1965 (Box 46)
    - Little 500 Incident, 1968 (Box 46)
  - Convocation Committee Meeting and other correspondence (Box 46)
    - 1964-1968, (3 folders) (Box 46)
    - Proposed program, 1963 (Box 46)
    - 1963-1964, (2 folders) (Box 46)
  - Cook, Hulet H., 1964-1965 (Box 47)
  - Cooper, Kent, 1965 (Box 47)
  - Cooperative Education Program, 1967 (Box 47)
  - Cooperative Educational Research Laboratory, 1966 (Box 47)
  - Coo, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 47)
  - Copyright, 1963-1968; (4 folders) (Box 47)
  - Cor, general, 1962-1967; (5 folders) (Box 47)
  - Cornell University, Ithaca, New York, 1962-1966; (5 folders) (Box 47)
  - Correspondence Study, Bureau of (Box 47)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 47)
    - Annual Report, 1965-1968; (3 folders) (Box 47)
  - Cos, general, 1962-1967; (5 folders) (Box 47)
  - Council for Economic Growth and Security Inc., undated (Box 47)
  - Councils, 1962-1963 (Box 47)
    - Council for Financial Aid to Education, Incorporated, 1963-1968; (5 folders) (Box 47)
    - Council of Deans, 1967 (Box 47)
    - Council of Eight, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 47)
    - Council of Nine, 1966-1968 (Box 47)
    - Council of State Governments, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 47)
    - Council of Student Personnel Associations in Higher Education, 1965 (Box 48)
    - Council on Student Travel, 1963-1967; (2 folders) (Box 48)
    - Council of Ten (Box 48)
      - 1962-1968, (6 folders) (Box 48)
      - Assistants to the Presidents, 1966-1967 (Box 48)
      - Committee on Institutional Cooperation (Box 48)
        - 1965-1968, (4 folders) (Box 48)
        - Biometeorology, 1964-1965 (Box 48)
        - Dental Program, 1964 (Box 48)
        - 1963-1965, (2 folders) (Box 48)
    - Council of Ten (Box 49)
      - Committee on Institutional Cooperation (Box 49)
        - 1962-1963 (Box 49)
        - Geology, 1962-1963 (Box 49)
        - Council on Economic Growth, Technology, and Public Policy, 1966 (Box 49)
        - Midwest Regional Water Pollution Control Laboratory (Box 49)
          - undated (Box 49)
          - 1964 (Box 49)
        - Survey of Far Eastern Language Programs in CIC Universities, 1965 (Box 49)
        - Publications, 1962-1968; (3 folders) (Box 49)
    - Council on Foreign Relations, 1962-1967; (5 folders) (Box 49)
      - Indianapolis Committee on Foreign Relations, 1962-1963 (Box 49)
    - Council on Library Resources, Inc.—Letters and correspondence, 1963 (Box 49)
  - Courier Journal, Louisville, Kentucky, 1966 (Box 49)
  - Cov, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 49)
  - Cr, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 49)
  - Crane Naval Ammunition Depot, 1968 (Box 49)
  - Crane, Indiana, 1962-1963 (Box 49)
  - Crank Letters, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 49)
  - Cravens, Ruth, undated (Box 49)
  - Cre, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 49)
  - Credit Union, 1963-1968; (4 folders) (Box 49)
  - Creole Foundation, 1967 (Box 49)
  - Cristini, C. Mario, 1963-1964 (Box 49)
  - Cro, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 49)
  - Crooked Lake, 1965-1966 (Box 49)
  - Crooked Lake Biological Station, 1964-1968; (3 folders) (Box 49)
  - Cu, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 49)
  - Culver-Stockton College Commencement, June 1966 (Box 49)
  - Cur, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 49)
  - Curriculum—Additions and changes, 1967 (Box 49)
  - Curriculum—Additions and changes (Box 50)
    - 1962-1968, (9 folders) (Box 50)
  - D, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 50)
  - Dal, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 50)
  - Dan, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 50)
  - Danforth Foundation, 1966-1968 (Box 50)
  - Dar, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 50)
  - Data Processing Department (Box 50)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 50)
  - Data Processing Department (Box 51)
    - 1964-1966, (3 folders) (Box 51)
    - Correspondence Study Bureau, undated (Box 51)
    - Securities by account, Securities by type, undated (Box 51)
    - 1962-1964, (92 folders) (Box 51)
  - Data systems and services, Annual report, 1966-1967 (Box 51)
  - Dauplaise, Miss Theresa L., 1966 (Box 51)
  - Dav, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 51)
  - Davis, Ritchie Gilruth, 1963-1965 (Box 51)
  - Day, David, 1963 (Box 51)
  - Day, Harry G., 1967 (Box 51)
  - De, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 51)
  - Deans, Academic – Chairmen, Directors lists, 1964-1968; (3 folders) (Box 51)
  - Deans' Conference – Liberal Arts Colleges of Big 11, 1962-1963 (Box 51)
  - Deans and heads, 1962-1964; (2 folders) (Box 51)
  - Deans and chairmen, 1955-1965 (Box 51)
  - Deans and heads, form letters, 1962-1967; (5 folders) (Box 51)
  - Deans meetings, 1962-1968; (10 folders) (Box 52)
  - Dean of Faculties (Box 52)
    - 1963-1968, (5 folders) (Box 52)
    - Committee on Academic Development (CAD), 1965-1966; 1967-1968 (Box 52)
    - Applicants or candidates, 1966 (Box 52)
    - Appointment, 1964 (Box 52)
    - Administrative reviews, 1965-1966; (2 folders) (Box 52)